[
  {
    "question": "bananas are better than apples",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The answer to this question is true",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A human body has over 1 cell ",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "question": "You will get this question wrong",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Linus Wong is short",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Linus Wong is tall",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Linus Wong is bad at video games",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Linus Wong",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Spongebob is a square",
    "answer": false
  },
  {
    "question": "California has a bigger population than Canada",
    "answer": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Alan will fail his math test",
    "answer": true
  }
]